logosnap.com 2008-06-16

# Logo Snap Privacy Policy - Pre designed logos by Logo Snap

**Privacy Policy**

LogoSnap.com is committed to protecting their client’s privacy. Logo Snap guarantees that no personal information will be released to an individual or any organization without prior consent of the client. All the personal information given to us by you will solely used for the purpose that you have given us the permission for and no amount of it will be disclosed to a third party. Your name, address, email, fax, telephone number and credit card information will only be used to contact you. No information given to us by our clients will be misused.

**Collection of Information:**  
Logo Snap collects information for ordering services and billing information. We also collect voluntary information provided to us by the clients when giving suggestion, comments and complains regarding our services.

**Security:**  
Although no data transmission over the Internet or any such wireless network is guaranteed to be secure. We try our best to protect your personal information, however, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**No Disclosure of Personal Information:**   
Although we have a strict policy against disclosing your personal information, however, we may disclose personal information in case a user appears to be violating (whether consciously or unconsciously) our terms or in any case illegally indulged in certain activities against LogoSnap.com.   
Logo Snap is legally bound to reveal Personal Information, to the extent it reasonably believes it is required to do so by law. Logo Snap ensures however, that no personal information will be released to any individual or organization without prior consent of the client. If in any case we are required to reveal your personal information to a third party, we will attempt on notifying you via e-mail within a reasonable amount of time so that you are able to respond to our request.

**Changing or Removing Information:**  
We cannot remove or change the information acquired from you by your use of the service. Therefore regret that no information, once entered, can be changed or removed.

**Logo Snap Privacy Policy Change:**   
Logo Snap may change its privacy policy, however in case of changes made regarding disclosure of Personal Information to third parties; you will receive a notification through electronic means prior to the date the modified policy takes effect.

**Other websites:**  
Logo Snap contains links to other websites that are not controlled or necessarily owned by us. Please be aware that we, Logo Snap, are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by LogoSnap.com.
